{"instructions": ["This section is an extended version of previous task, which is clicking on the <strong>WORD</strong> prompted by the voice. <p></p>In cases where you can not hear the word, just give your best guess.", "When you are ready, click <strong>Continue</strong> to hear the first word."], "feedback": true, "holdfeedback": false, "feedbackdur": 600, "serveraudio": false, "estimatedduration": 4, "randomize": false, "isi": 600, "volume": [{"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "Let us adjust the volume one more time for louder sounds. Please lower down your volume first.", "choices": ["Continue"]}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Now adjust your computer volume up to a comfortable (but not too loud) level.", "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/volume.wav", "choices": ["I have adjusted the volume, let's continue"]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "Is the right headphone in your right ear, and the left headphone in your left ear? It is very important!", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue."]}], "trials": [{"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heave", "hear", "heat", "heal", "heap", "heath"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_8_29_6_Pkii61skZHKYU8DM.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["puff", "puck", "pub", "pus", "pup", "pun"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_-4_33_6_5ngbxUax3jqKTlt0.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["same", "name", "game", "tame", "came", "fame"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_14_26_1_m6WfPY21Ix2lJ4Bf.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kit", "bit", "fit", "hit", "wit", "sit"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_-10_5_2_9XGIldZvBcPbBmR2.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bed", "led", "fed", "red", "wed", "shed"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_8_9_4_sFiwHbbTsTPX1ucn.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["took", "cook", "look", "hook", "shook", "book"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_-10_39_1_PUeD1fpvwbbIxmRP.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fun", "sun", "bun", "gun", "run", "nun"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_-4_50_5_shwFEtRiYZwEDPwS.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["bean", "beach", "beat", "beak", "bead", "beam"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_-10_34_1_2GYkRNo4zuF0DDVH.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["shop", "mop", "cop", "top", "hop", "pop"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_2_22_1_HiIhoQELMF7paaGs.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["heat", "neat", "feat", "seat", "meat", "beat"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_-4_35_5_PeajjA7E7v0AzZRT.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fill", "kill", "will", "hill", "till", "bill"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_14_43_3_oqhOZCCkjC8eEmFC.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["kill", "kin", "kit", "kick", "king", "kid"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_2_37_3_plRsoSX3huzGolpe.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["back", "bath", "bad", "bass", "bat", "ban"], "answer": 6, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_2_17_6_Fy4UW9uNKYbO1ZEv.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["mass", "math", "map", "mat", "man", "mad"], "answer": 3, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_2_40_3_IjUpEzxPwBHFCb91.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "2", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["thaw", "law", "raw", "paw", "jaw", "saw"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_8_31_2_hCWTDaPteUWcLfq3.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["fit", "fib", "fizz", "fill", "fig", "fin"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_8_25_4_JX77Z4OE99rS5Fq6.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "8", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["not", "tot", "got", "pot", "hot", "lot"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_14_14_2_Xreh2055wG7VFpcv.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["way", "may", "say", "pay", "day", "gay"], "answer": 4, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_-4_18_4_stLQusPXaa44KrqF.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-4", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["vest", "test", "rest", "best", "west", "nest"], "answer": 5, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_-10_15_5_0ccU28SRjh9kV3H1.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"SNR": "-10", "condition": "echo-ref"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "Select the <strong>word</strong> prompted by the voice", "choices": ["save", "same", "sale", "sane", "sake", "safe"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/wordInNoise/follow-up/echo-ref_14_42_2_RFyzr8z6Sd26Q4xI.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"SNR": "14", "condition": "echo-ref"}}]}